Said this could explode.
>> We spent a thousand dollars on Temu.
Focusing on the cheapest, the weirdest,
and what could be the scammiest products
on the app. We've got everything from
this robot dog to knockoff batteries and
even a remote-controlled lawnmower. The
cost $485.
All hairs. All to answer the question,
is Temu still the dumpster of the
internet when it comes to buying
anything? Well, we're going to find out.
We're testing all of it and we're
ranking all of it so you don't have to
waste your time and money. This should
be fun. So, here's what we got. A table
full
of random garbage. At least that's what
it looked like.
Including this beautiful boxed-up
lawnmower here that Sam is more than
excited to get into. We're going to be
ranking these things one to 10. One
being a scam, 10 being you should put it
in your house immediately.
We need to figure out if we need to get
rid of this Temu app [music] on
everybody's phone. I don't have it.
Sam's got three phones, all Temu apps
only. So, up first, let's crack into
this mower. Get this ready to rock
and roll. The sun finally came out in
Pittsburgh, which means it's
grass-cutting season.
Oh, boy.
Okay.
>> [laughter]
>> Straight out of the box, we have what I
think could be the greatest visual
representation
of anything I've ever seen in my life
on a user guide. [music] Can you believe
that? What are you doing down there?
>> I'm going to get the remote.
>> Look at this. [music]
>> Oh, wow. That looks like looks like
cursed early '90s animation. Like 3D
animation.
>> like the least amount of effort possible
could have been put into to that. You
know what? I'm wrong. It looks exactly
like the robot.
>> Does it? I'm excited for that. I've got
high hopes for that the
remote-controlled lawnmower.
>> of it. I just don't have any hope
for Temu
servicing one that's any good.
>> Ugh.
>> [laughter]
>> This thing feels so shitty. It feels
like I'm playing with a kid's toy.
>> Is that a push button start on there?
>> It is a push button start.
>> Oh, wow. It's like a BMW.
>> So, blades have covers on them, thank
goodness. I can't believe this is all it
is. Check this out, Sam. Touch this.
Just Just touch it.
>> Wow, it looks like metal, but that's the
most plastic plastic that money can buy.
>> That is the cheapest, shittiest, and
worst
>> plastic you could put on anything.
>> All right, so it looks like it's battery
powered, which means we got to charge
this thing up. We've got a first look.
There's not much to it.
Sam's excited. Maybe we'll have a little
race with our traditional push and and
this old girl here. Um so, let's get
this charged up. We'll jump into
something else.
Next, we have the dragon blade, as you
can see here. This is every bit of what
it's described as.
Gorgeous, sturdy,
well-made.
It It's actually none of that. This
thing is a complete utter piece of What
did this cost?
>> $3.37.
>> This was $3?
>> Careful. Once it's unsheathed, it must
taste human flesh.
>> It just sounds
shitty.
So,
it says on the listing, "It's a
one-piece for one-piece forged dragon
head chef's knife, a 10-in
boning knife with ergonomic handle,
ideal for cutting meat and vegetables,
heavy-duty home cutting tool, a unique
gift for chefs."
I'm just going to go out on a limb here.
I don't think this is a single forged
piece, as well as I do believe
I could just snap the metal in half. And
yes, that was the metal that broke.
Don't [snorts] you hate it when that
happens?
>> Look how much it bends.
>> There's nothing I like more with my
chef's knives than being able to snap
them in half by hand. You could feel it
in the tang, [music]
how shitty that thing was. Joe hates
when I just come straight into a video
and snap something. He at least wanted
to see it cut, I think. If you got me a
Give me a banana, let's see.
Just throw it the away. God, go on
to the next video of the world.
>> to have to give this one a [music] one
complete other scam, even four. You can
get way better blades for four bucks.
>> Next. Next we've got a portable sealing
machine, and I wouldn't be surprised if
this was just
straight out of the '80s in not only the
quality of the box, but the way it
looks. This thing just looks like an As
Seen on TV product that we bought for a
previous video. It's got a bunch of
really weird writing on the back that is
like
hard to read. Check this out.
Ooh, she's charged up. It's got a magnet
on it.
That That's the weakest magnet in
history.
Oh, wow.
>> I've got faith in this one, though. This
one I think could be useful. Yeah.
>> It seems like pretty solid.
>> listing says that it's a set of two
snack bag sealers. Where's my
second [music] sealer?
>> Well, it has two buttons.
I don't know.
>> What?
>> It's the only thing I see in double. I
got a single.
>> Hold Hold How about that? Set of two
snack bag sealers includes one sealer
and one charging cable. So, the set of
two is including [laughter] the charger.
Temu, what the kind of listing is
that?
>> Technically not false advertising.
>> Temu, what the hell are you doing? It's
got a built-in lithium ion battery, low
power consumption, manual magnetic
design, suitable for home, picnics,
outings, travel, portability, silent and
efficient chip [music] and cookie bag
sealer. It's got a little knife in
there, I think, to open.
Should we try that?
>> I don't know. I don't I don't think it's
to open.
>> I think it is. What the hell else would
it be
>> it's maybe whenever you seal it, it cuts
off like a clean edge.
>> it makes it clean.
>> Oh.
Okay.
Me. Well, the directions aren't written
in English.
>> Brush up on your Mandarin.
What do we go with here? Martins?
From Thomasville, PA.
Did someone send these to us?
I've never heard of these.
>> No, we just got them from the grocery
store this morning.
>> Were they just the cheapest ones you
could find?
>> I told Ryan to get the most ridiculous
bag of chips he could find.
>> And this is what he thought of?
>> Yes, they're gluten-free.
>> All chips are gluten-free.
But these aren't bad.
So, she's on. I wonder if it needs a
heat up time.
I guess you just squeeze it down.
Oh, it's working.
Oh, it's working. How are we going to
keep it lined up?
>> Oh, the knife makes sense. I guess it's
the further you get down into the chips,
you can keep lowering it and lowering
it.
>> Yeah, that makes sense.
There was a huge, I feel like in the
'90s this was like the most common
product ever.
Like, reseal your bag of chips. Stop
wasting money on on chips that go bad.
You know your fat ass at home is eating
the chips regardless if they're stale or
not. No one's throwing that out. Me
three.
I never once looked at a bag of chips
and said, "Oh, those are stale. Get rid
of them." IT DOES WORK THOUGH.
WOW!
FOR SO, THIS WAS ON
WHAT?
On sale from $20.49
to $3.24.
I'm going to have to give this like a
six. It's scammy in every way, but it
gets the job done. I guess now we have
to reopen with it. Do we just go like
this?
Ah.
Bag's ruined now. Drop it to a five.
It's only cuz the magnet's so weak. But
we're going to keep it here just in case
Sam needs to seal some bags.
Unbelievable. Next, we got a 10-m
>> [laughter]
>> fluorescent, see-through
tape measure
on sale from $16.59 to $3.39
on the old Temu.
This thing says high precision
self-locking fluorescent tape measure
196.85
in
275.59
in 393.7
in laser I don't know why it just keeps
listing random inches laser inkjet code
box design ABS resin 0.1 mm accuracy.
I'm glad that we're measuring in feet
and imperial units yet we're using
millimeter accuracy clear view display
suitable for building and measuring tool
width.
That makes a lot of sense there. It's
got four and a half stars
on Temu.
>> All right.
>> For $3.39.
So straight out of the gate my favorite
thing is it says 196.85 in and it's all
in metric.
>> [sighs]
>> No I got I hate it when that happens
don't you?
>> Is the bottom in inches?
>> Nope.
>> [laughter]
>> It's kind of nice to have a metric tape
here now.
>> He's not wrong. Straight out of the gate
the tab on it is gigantic on both sides.
It's not very good.
It's all yeah it's metric. It's huge in
your hand. You have to have a massive
hand.
>> This isn't bad.
>> So where did I don't even know what
these are 260 270 280
>> [snorts]
>> Lost a nipple.
>> Didn't need them anyway.
>> My favorite part of it so far though is
the branding.
It's just incredible. It is kind of
neat.
I mean for three bucks I could see I
could see it working. It feels pretty
flimsy. Like I'm spreading the box
with my thumbs
>> [music]
>> just by squeezing it.
>> Oh yeah. Let's see how it does with a
drop test.
Survived. Survived.
>> See if you can close it.
>> Yep.
>> All right.
>> Yep. Does she still work?
>> It heals itself.
>> Nope. The lock broke.
>> We didn't need that. [music]
>> We didn't.
>> Give it time, and it'll heal.
>> Please don't take that out.
>> Why?
Don't you want one of these in your in
your life?
>> No.
>> No?
>> This is what they use inside of like
kids' bracelets.
>> The snap bracelet.
>> you to go find a snap bracelet
manufacturer and DONATE THAT, PLEASE.
I'M GOING TO HAVE TO GIVE THAT ONE
A THREE.
Um
You got to be able to crowbar your tape
measure off of a door.
It's it's a it's a requirement.
>> What have we got next?
>> We have ourselves here the USB 5-volt
motion sensor LED light strip neon light
decoration with chasing effect for
kitchen cabinet stairs bedrooms and
proposal party decor LED lights for
bedroom kitchen lighting modern
illumination stylish design energy
saving lighting. It rolls right off the
tongue. It's a great product. It's uh
from the fine folks at Foshan Yee
Lighting Technology Company.
Um
they're known for
>> dare rip that out.
>> pretty good product, so I'm expecting
nothing but the best from them. So,
to my understanding, these are motion
sensing lights, and I believe in their
advertising, they showed them as going
under your stair treads. But, I have a
question. That's not enough for a full
staircase. And then what happens when
you get it on one step? Do you just have
to tuck it and run it to the next and
the next and how how much was this? This
was $10.93.
>> I've got low hopes for this out of the
gate.
>> I'm quite disappointed, Foshan Yee
Lighting.
>> Are you ready, Jeff?
>> Send it.
>> Okay, that's worth it just to
>> did that every time with the motion, we
might be talking.
>> All right, let's see.
Okay, it's a timer.
Okay, 15 [music] seconds night time. Sit
here and wait.
>> A little longer than a few minutes
later.
>> We've consulted the user manual. We
followed the the directions. The motion
sensor, it's very hit or miss. We got to
work one time, but we can't get it to
work again. I I would not buy this
product. I even think this is overpriced
for just like a 6-ft strip of LEDs, 10
bucks. Don't buy this. I rate this a
one. You are a scam, and you are
banished to where all the scam products
go, the fiery pits of hell.
On to the next one.
>> Next we have a curved phone screen
amplifier.
If something's ever screamed a scam to
me, this is it.
>> [laughter]
>> Who the hell calls an external screen a
screen amplifier?
>> [laughter]
>> The listing, well, I'll just pop it up
right here. It's foldable.
It's got 3D magnification and adjustable
What the
>> Whoa.
>> What the is this? I'm trying not
to cuss on here. I got stopped four
times at the Masters. People are like,
"I can't watch my stuff with your kid my
kids."
Uh It's
>> [laughter]
>> It's a giant magnifying glass. It's an
actual magnifier. You got to be kidding
me.
I This thing cost $3 It's $40.
>> No.
>> No, on sale for $3.88.
>> It's curved, and so it gives like
um
>> [music]
>> magnification. We could probably roast
some ants with it if we wanted.
>> All right.
Technically
>> shitty.
>> Should we try with the lights off?
>> We put it on YouTube. You know, GO GET
[music] THE LIGHTS.
>> NO, GET THOSE LIGHTS OFF. SO, SAY YOU
WANT TO GO movie theater-esque
and you want [music] to get your
Unscrewed fix on.
I got to be honest.
It's swinging [music] above its weight
class here, people. I'm getting rid of
all the TVs in my house. I'm just going
to amplify my cell phone.
>> [music]
>> You just got to be a little closer, and
it actually works very well.
>> Yeah, it's like you would amplify it to
be further away, yet the only way to get
it to be clear is to be this close.
So, might as well just stick your phone
in your face. It has a very weird hue.
[music]
Like it creates a lot of rainbows. I
can't call it a scam, though.
Hit the lights. I need to read the box.
>> we need the lights off still for the
other product. It's a two-for-one
product.
>> about to do what I think [music] we're
about to do?
>> Go ahead, plug it in. You'll see what it
is. It's a surprise.
>> This is an extra?
>> Yeah.
>> Bonus!
So, we got a USB.
What do I plug it into?
>> A USB port.
>> Oh, well, that's how that works.
Hmm.
Oh, wow.
The moon!
>> It's the moon. There it is.
>> Is it the moon?
>> Can you point it at your logo?
>> Wow. What is it supposed What is this?
>> It's the moon. It's supposed to be the
moon.
>> to be that?
>> Try against the toolbox in the short
range.
>> It has no details. Even the moon looks
more detailed to the naked eye than
that.
>> [laughter]
>> That's rough.
>> Right? It's just a It's just a circle.
How dare they sell Did they sell that as
the moon?
>> Yes, they did.
>> Those lying bastards. That's 100% a
scam. Sam, get this out of my presence
right now. [music] This Don't lie to me.
It's a monumental time to be an
American,
specifically when regards to the moon.
You're going to lie to me with that
junk?
>> Hold on. Can we hit the lights real
quick, Bola?
>> So, you have to be in the complete dark.
What's this box? Where's the box?
>> Yeah, the box says two to three times
bigger, but eye protection.
>> I thought it said butt with two b's when
you read it out loud. Butt eye
protection.
>> your butt protection.
>> and anti-broken.
>> Very nice.
>> Easy to use, yes. I'm giving
I can only give it a six at max. A six.
>> That's our leader right now.
>> It is our leader right now. It's not a
complete utter scam. It's just the
dumbest thing I think we've ever
purchased. [music]
Does it magnify my face?
Next!
Up next, we've got a a multi-functional
flashlight here.
>> got to go back. We got to go back to the
last product because there are little
screens to to show the moon.
>> OH MY GOODNESS.
>> WE CAN'T give it a fair review.
>> we didn't give the moon a fair review?
>> No, not at all.
>> Well, plug it in for the sake of all
things important.
>> Dan, hit the lights.
>> Uh that's a considerably better moon.
>> actually way better.
>> All right, I'll go up to a three. It's
not a
Yeah, man. It's still scary as I
want to have to have it plugged into a
receptacle that holds a USB.
>> You can hit them, Dan.
>> Back to the multi-functional flashlight
here. We've got a beam of tech with a
world of brightness. That's some
marketing if I've ever heard it. This
thing looks like Iron Man took a dump
and a flashlight came out and I kind of
love it. It's actually made of metal. It
Feel that, Joe. It actually feels solid.
It doesn't feel like every other plastic
piece of junk.
We probably paid a premium for this
sucker, huh?
>> Supposedly, it's meant for starting
fires.
>> 16 what? $16 on sale for $12.40.
I'm not even going to read what it says
there. I'm just going to look at this
photo where there are flames.
Which means
that's an instant headache.
Is there any disclaimer on not sticking
it in your eyes?
>> Probably.
>> Here's the whole [music] user manual.
This is the best part, guys.
>> Look at the email. It's just a dude
named Joe Beewee at 163.com.
If you've ever wanted all of your
information on your computer stolen,
that's the email you need to send an
email to right now. Joe Beewee
>> Joe Beewee at 163.com. [music]
Wow.
>> Well, let's get a pile of stuff to go
light on fire. What do you say, Sam?
>> I I've already got a bucket with sawdust
ready for the fire.
>> Welcome to John's wild and wonderful
world of outdoors ridiculous dumb
that we've built that just sits here and
collects dust. We're going to light the
dust on fire now.
We've got
I don't know if it has like
That looks like it's full max.
>> Yeah, it is.
>> And now I just hold it It does hurt the
eyes.
>> Yeah, the
>> look at it. I wish I didn't give my only
pair of shop shades dimmers to Sam to
shoot an ad last week because now I
don't have them anymore.
But you can get a pair of John
Maleki.com. They are available now.
I'll just stare blindly into the sun
while you
run away with my beautiful dimmers.
>> I got to
>> smoking yet?
>> I'm not even I can't even tell. Might
want to just leave it there.
>> Okay.
This is upsetting.
>> Why is that their marketing tactic? You
light a fire with this flashlight.
>> You calling out our boy Joe Beewee?
>> Yeah, Joe Beewee, if you're out there,
I'd like to have some words with you.
>> What kind of bamboozlement is this, Joe
Beewee? All right, we've been out here
for a good solid 37 minutes. Nothing's
happening. I think we're going to have
to call this one.
>> The flashlight itself is a solid 100°.
[music]
>> I'm just saying. I I can't hold it
anymore.
>> Golly, here Sam. Get
Sam.
Iron Man's turd.
Joe Beewee, I can't believe you'd lie to
me like that.
>> What we got next?
>> Hey,
it's giveaway time. Right now, you can
get entered to win this 791 piece fully
kitted out mechanics tool set from
Gearwrench. We've partnered with Ohio
Power Tool and could not be more
excited. Look at these gorgeous
organizers. Every dollar you spend on
John Maleki.com right now can get you
entered to win this thing. And this bad
boy can be in your shop soon. All the
rules and regulations are in the link
down below. There's no purchase
necessary to get entered to win, so
check it out at JohnMaleki.com or the QR
code on the screen. Next, I have a piece
of paper [music]
that cost $117.
Is this real?
>> Uh we ordered it
and it never showed up.
>> What?
>> Yeah.
>> It's a full medieval
barbuda knight armor suit with crusader
steel barbuda helmet and plate wearable
larp
re-enactment costume did not show up?
>> They refunded it after a month.
>> Oh, what a shame. I highly doubt my
giant physique would fit inside it
anyways. That would have been hilarious.
Damn it. Well, you Temu. Anyone got
a suit of armor they want to donate for
us?
Just let us know. Get you hooked up.
Appreciate it.
>> [music]
>> Next.
Next we've got a
automatic ejection building blocks gun.
What?
>> One for the whole family.
>> Let's go. A Lego 9 mm
.40 cal. This is hilarious.
This is cool as This cost $9.76.
I think it's a You actually have a full
slide here. You've got a safety lock on
this side.
>> You have to hold the green tab down when
you shoot it, as stupid as that is.
>> Yeah, that.
>> Okay. Automatic ejection building blocks
gun with bullet casting stem
construction set with realistic bullet
launcher mechanism. Safe non-poisonous
building blocks for teens and adults.
Parents children assembly kit. 2025
Christmas birthday gift for boys and
Nothing after the end, but
All right.
Let's put this thing together.
Now, you want to talk Legos?
Let's talk Legos. So, we've got six
little bullets here.
A bunch of random Lego pieces. I wonder
if this is Lego sanctioned.
>> [snorts]
[laughter]
>> I don't think so.
>> doubt that. I just love that there's
just like random
Legos. All right.
Load up the magazine.
Would you look at that, huh?
Would you look at that?
>> [laughter]
>> That was so fun.
Oh, that one didn't work.
>> That's a
Where is it shooting?
>> hell is going on?
>> I think this is a little backwards.
>> Okay. Not a single one of those worked.
Huh. Um
Okay, let's try that again.
Okay.
>> I think you just shoot it. I think it'll
just work.
All right.
Oh, we got a jam.
>> I had high hopes for this thing.
>> [music]
>> It mildly works. Should work way easier,
right?
>> Well, should is a very strong word to
use for a T-Mod Lego gun.
>> True.
What it was the price?
>> $10.20
key cents.
>> for 10 bucks it just looks cool.
So, I'm giving it a seven.
>> What? [laughter]
What the
>> I think I'll take the lead.
>> That's the highest score yet.
>> For something that doesn't even
work?
>> I'm in a good mood.
Ha. Ha. Rain the winner.
>> It actually have a little oomph to it.
>> Let's go. Six.
Next. Sam, I have a surprise for you.
>> All right.
>> This one specifically, I thought, you
know, you would enjoy this for phone
calls.
>> I've wanted to try one of these for so
long, and it's red, too.
Ah, come on now.
I still There were still phones with
cords when I was growing up. I haven't
seen one of these in a minute.
>> [snorts]
>> So, I just plug this right into my
>> cellular?
>> Operator? Operator, connect me to John
Maleky.
John, it's your new business manager,
Ray Thomas. Things are going
gangbusters. We took out a headline in
the Pittsburgh Post-Gazette. John
Malecki does it again. We've had three
written inquiries since Yes, three
written inquiries.
I'll talk to you soon, sir. Farewell.
Have yourself a Manhattan ON ME.
WE'LL ACTUALLY TEST THE PRODUCT NOW.
>> [laughter]
>> GO FOR a walk, Bobby.
I just want to see how good the audio
quality is.
>> All right, just call me here. I'll put
you on speaker.
Oh, wow, that's the quality.
>> Yeah, it's a little muffled.
>> Yeah, it sounds terrible. I can still
understand you and everything, but Oh,
here he comes now.
>> What are your final thoughts?
>> Now, I kind of like the idea of this for
someone that like for example, they're
like, "Hey, you know what? I don't want
to use my phone after like 7:00 at
night. I'll just have it sit here like
this. If someone calls me, I'll answer
it, but otherwise
just sits there.
I like the idea of that product. This
one specifically could be a little
better, but it's not bad. I'm going to
give it a five. Five out of 10.
Does what it says relatively well.
>> I'd say four, a little lower.
Quality's just a little muffled.
>> Yeah, the quality is kind of muffled.
Oh, oh, and you There's a hang up
button.
>> Oh, wow.
>> I also think that might be a motion
sensor. So, if it's ringing, you could
just
Hello.
I don't know if it Do you want to test
it real quick before we move on? Oh, let
me turn my volume on.
>> [music]
>> Hold on.
Hello.
>> Try pressing the button.
>> Hello.
Okay, that's kind of cool.
All right, I'll give it a five. Let's
go.
On to the next one.
>> Next, we've got what looks to be
fantastic
clock rug. Is that what this says?
>> Supposed to tell you the weather and
time.
>> One piece modern doormat suitable for
bedroom, kitchen, bathroom entrance,
soft washable floor with temperature and
weather display.
Machine washable backing [snorts]
and suitable for home decor, suitable
for office use. I love the commas here.
Incredible. It says, "Machine washable
backing, \comma} suitable for home
decor, \comma} suitable for office,
\comma} use, \comma} holiday gift."
All right. So, uh
here she is.
It just says this all the time.
>> [laughter]
>> 1852, quite a year.
>> They advertise it like it change like
it's a LED panel.
>> Wow, this is a
piece of junk. There's no nothing
reviews. There's nothing digital about
it. I'm very disappointed. From an
American.
Very dumb. From another American. And
then we've got Cindy who got cut off who
gave it five stars.
Hey Cindy.
What drugs are you on?
We want in.
What is That's a That's a zero. This is
the scamiest scam of all scams. It
actually feels
more like a towel than it does a rug.
Here you go, pull it. You can give that
to your cat.
>> Yeah, nice.
>> Yeah, you're welcome. What have we got
next? Up next, we've got a fun one here.
This
is the scam of all scams potentially.
We've got two 20-V [music]
lithium ion replacement batteries for
DeWalt cordless drills.
Compatible with the
DCB200, DCB205,
DCB206,
and more.
>> What else?
>> [music]
>> Workshop equipment power tool accessory
durable construction tool accessory
long-lasting charge handy high-capacity
one-word battery rechargeable battery
pack tool battery pack.
$76 on sale for $23.45.
These, ladies and gentlemen, are what
are burning down shops all over the
world.
If you have been seeing why
workshops are catching on fire when
batteries are being charged, it's
because
like this [music] is out there in
the world and people have no clue.
So, looking at it, the bottom
we've got Li-ion
industry leader in lithium ion.
Um somehow this is European certified.
We know that cuz Shop Series are also
European certified. And uh you have to
pay for that badge, so
you're doing Europe. Rechargeable
lithium ion battery DCB200 20 V 8 Ah.
For safe operation, see instruction
manual. Use high-capacity charger.
Charging room temperature is 10° C to
40° C.
Don't get it wet. Don't throw it away.
>> [music]
>> Recyclable.
And then it's got a 1-800 number for
recycling. It's made in China. Looks and
feels Well, looks like a a a DeWalt
battery. The instruction manual number
seven here is pretty good. It says only
use charge the battery [music] with the
charger. No together. Use with other
type of charger may result in [music] a
fire.
Do not crush, drop, or damage the
battery pack. Do not use a battery pack
or charger that has been dropped or
received a sharp blow. A damaged battery
[music] is subject to explosion.
What?
Use only batteries with the voltage
listed on the name plate of your power
tool. Using other batteries can lead to
injuries and pose a fire hazard. I
wonder if this shit's on normal battery.
[music] Stop. Give me that. It's 20 V.
Okay. You're good.
So, these are charged.
Nice snug tight fit.
I mean, it works.
Oh.
Here's the thing though.
If it gets damaged or dropped, like you
need your batteries to have some balls.
Said this could explode.
Didn't explode.
I'm so actually surprised the casing
didn't blow up.
It sur- It survived me hooking it off a
wall.
>> Why is everything I get hooked off the
wall?
>> Well, Sam, you can't test It says that
if it gets dropped, it could explode.
Obviously, we have to test it.
>> it were to explode in the shop?
>> That'd [music] be bad.
>> Yeah, boy.
>> At least we have it on video for now. I
am having surgery next week, so we could
just double up if I were to blow my hand
off or something, you know.
>> Two for one?
>> Two for one, yeah. Keep that insurance
rate down. Excuse me real quick, guys. I
need to caffeinate.
>> It looks remarkably similar to the OG
DeWalt battery.
>> Can you tell which ones are fake?
>> I can, but if they were
they were both pretty dirty, I don't
know.
At a at a moment's moment's glance
>> on the side doesn't give it away?
>> Yeah, but I'm saying just like
>> the bottom?
>> Uh
>> Where this one says Li-ion?
>> [laughter]
>> It's the new It's the new the new
lithium ion.
>> It's pretty wild. [music] I mean, I
can't call it a scam for honestly
because they say exactly what they are.
They're a replacement battery for
DeWalt. They don't claim to be a DeWalt
battery except for the fact they're the
exact same colors as DeWalt tools.
It gives you the disclosure on it. I
wouldn't buy these. I would not put
these in my shop, my house. I wouldn't
put these anywhere near my life. Let's
take one apart.
Let's see what's on the inside.
>> Okay.
>> Well, okey-dokey. So, we open this
sucker up and
it looks pretty uh
pretty normal. Do we have a DeWalt
battery we could open that we wouldn't
up putting back together? The only
thing that I expect to see inside of a a
DeWalt battery is a little bit more in
regards to the like the packaging. I
also find it interesting, Sam. Do you
see that they they're claiming this is
an 8 amp hour battery that's the exact
same size as a 5 amp hour.
>> Yeah, I believe that.
>> got an 8 amp hour over there.
>> We got a 10.
>> Bring the 10. This has 10 cells. I don't
know how amp hours work, but if smart
people like Yianni is out there,
probably do. And uh I'm too busy right
now to use AI to tell me what it is. So,
we're just going to go with 10 cells
equals 8 amps of hour.
This is a 10 amp hour DeWalt battery.
This is their XR. And then this is our
Chinese knockoff 8 amp hour battery.
Um significant size difference for two
like this is 3 amp hour difference to
this, same exact size. 2 amp hour
difference to this, giant size. Do I
know why? No.
God.
>> Yeah, they look
>> Gods dammit.
>> Very similar.
>> So, I guess the big difference Oh, oh,
it's there. I was going to say
this one
the motherboards are in different
locations.
The soldering on the DeWalt has seen a
few things, poor guy.
It's corroded.
It looks like the connections are in a
little bit different area. I What do you
Is that a heat happening element?
There. This just looks like the DeWalt
battery has a bigger motherboard. This
is kind of like what I was saying about
the connections before. There's some
insulation in there, which you don't see
on this. This is just directly That's
kind of This is [music] a
locked in.
This is not. So, where batteries explode
is like these things
heat up
>> [music]
>> and the cells crack from the heating up
and some other junk happens, I think. Um
but like loose connections are never
good.
>> [music]
>> I just personally I can't endorse the I
have to give them a zero.
I have to give them a one. I can't allow
the good people of Unscrewed to invest
in these with me telling them to. So,
I'm I'm sorry, guys and and girls. You
can buy these if you want,
>> [music]
>> but don't say
Jimalexi said to buy them.
Next.
>> This next product is one I'm extremely
excited for.
It is a a web shooter. However, unlike
the silly string ones we had
growing up, this one actually It a
retractable line and a suction cup in
the Spider-Man glove. It makes you feel
really bad if you purchase this as an
adult because then you get the glove and
it's child-sized and you put it on and
you go,
"What am I doing with my life? Why did I
order this Spider-Man web shooter off
Temu?" We'll We'll do one test here and
I can think of no better test but to
go around and surprise web team members.
3 2 1 Go web, go.
>> [snorts]
>> They gave us an extra suction cup. That
popped right Oh, wait.
Joe, there's a magnet. [music]
Wait a minute. Hold on.
I think it wasn't close enough.
Sorry.
Technical error.
>> [snorts]
Uh the magnet's working. It's stuck to
something. What's it stuck to? Okay.
>> A piece of metal?
>> If we should just progress to webbing
the teammates.
Uh here, let me stick a suction cup on
there.
What are you doing here, Green Goblin? I
thought I told you to stay out of New
York City. Apparently, you can't learn
lessons the easy way. So, we'll do them
the hard way. Yeah. Yeah, got you. Got
him. It worked flawlessly. Oh, please,
miss. I'll open this hot dog roller door
for you.
This doesn't usually happen.
You're just so gorgeous. I was
distracted.
No match for my web shooter. Yeah.
I'll leave now. Excuse myself from here.
>> What would you rate it?
>> This is a 10 out of 10. This is so much
[snorts] fun. I could do this all day.
>> [laughter]
>> All right, last test, the swing test.
After this, onto the next.
>> We have AI smart glasses. Joe, you know
>> Shop Shades are permanently fused to my
face.
>> I know, that's why we have Sam here.
>> And his.
>> They're not on him. We They've seen him
without his Shop Shades.
>> Okay.
Straight out of the box, packaging sub
par, nowhere close to as nice as Shop
Shades.
>> I had to charge them and put them back.
>> I'm still blaming the box.
They are C E U K C A F C
not A N S I Z 87 plus.
They're tiny.
They come with
two bag a bag and a microfiber towel.
And a buttload of instructions.
Excuse me while we circumnavigate the
globe.
Mr. Pua, if you don't mind.
People think I'm joking. I sleep with
Shop I bathe with Shop Shades on. My
daughters
they're like, "Dad
why are you in the swimming pool with
your Shop Shades on?" And I'm like, "You
never know when your eyes are going to
be in danger, dear."
All right, so the directions say
AI real-time translation glasses, couple
smart glasses, stylish BT headphones,
fashion accessory for men and women, an
auto-dimming lens, music playback,
wireless calls, voice assistant
activation, camera remote control,
perfect Valentine's Day gift.
>> on that?
>> They are $19.88.
You got to connect it to Bluetooth.
>> You love connecting your phone to random
Bluetooth.
>> I have so much Chinese spyware on my
phone from all these products.
>> So here's the directions. Bear with me.
Glasses temples pairing
It's exactly what it says.
>> Should a light flash or something?
>> power on, two sides glasses temples
paired automatically.
>> So wait wait over here. GSS7 maybe
that's it.
>> Connected device, turn on wireless,
search and select G Y star star star
star star from detected devices. It's
got magnetic charging ports. There's no
other directions.
>> All right, we're we're connected.
Let's try to live translate. Joe, can
you lead me to the nearest watering hole
in this fine town?
>> It's just an app. You don't even need
the glasses for that.
>> So, is it using the microphone on the
app
or on the on the eyeglasses? What are
the glasses doing that?
>> I don't know. You say there's a camera
on here?
>> I but the thing said he read. They're
scams. Let's go.
>> Is it playing anything in your ear?
>> I I could make it play things. It's not
playing it very well.
>> I can't rate them. I'm not allowed. It's
coming down to you, Sam.
One to 10.
>> One. One. It's horrible. Yeah. It's a
scam.
>> You know who doesn't agree with you?
Grissel Camacho Centrone thinks it's an
excellent purchase and that they're very
beautiful and work perfectly. Truly one
of the best [music] purchases
they've ever made.
>> I I highly doubt that.
>> face.
>> I highly doubt that.
>> You're out of control. Next. Finally,
the smart dog. This came in at $194.64.
But it was on sale for $34. Suck on
that, Elon Musk.
Look at that gem, huh?
Yeah.
Let's go.
What?
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah.
>> That's going to need batteries. The
listing: Intelligent Robot Dog. 2.4 GHz
remote control toy dog with a maximum
remote control distance of 99 ft. AI
voice control can be connected
programming actions to mobile apps. It
can dance,
telling stories, perform a dance.
These are just the stupidest stupidest
things ever.
We got reviews that say they love this
guy.
Tons of fun with the kids and adults.
Best buy, love it. Exactly as described.
Fast shipping. Temu the truth. Great
prices. Received it and out it into use.
>> Try turning her on.
>> Who are they? I can't.
>> Is there on-and-off switch on it.
>> Oh.
She's screaming.
Hurry up on that remote.
>> This would actually be hilarious with
like like pets. I feel like they would
get like freaked out
>> wouldn't give a My
Maggie would lose her mind screaming.
She'd be so scared of this. 35 bucks?
All right, so this thing does greetings,
swimming, handstand, attack dog, sit
down, and my favorite, kung fu.
That's about the same size as your dogs.
>> Yeah. Oh,
he's This is supposed to be kung fu?
>> Is that kung fu?
>> Yeah.
>> I think he flipped over by accident,
Pula.
Are you sure you should own a dog?
>> I don't know, man.
Oh, there he is. Now he's doing kung
>> What are you doing, Sam?
>> trying to point it to the camera.
>> It's taking a piss.
>> This is extremely impressive.
>> This is hilarious. What is it doing on
the floor?
>> I think it was a thrust.
>> What are you doing? Back that thing up.
Can it sense things?
>> It doesn't have like a forward and
reverse. Like here's forward,
but I can't bring him back. Stop.
Stop.
>> it sensed it.
>> Oh, did it?
>> Yeah.
It's taking a leak on the fridge.
>> [laughter]
>> What is that?
>> I don't know.
Oh, wait, here I can make him urinate.
Urinate.
>> What if it peed?
All right, Sam.
Training time's over. Make her dance.
>> Robot, dance.
>> [laughter]
>> Yes. Yes.
>> I
I kind of love it.
I think the only lies
for me so far the
AI voice control thing. We just can't
figure that out.
>> No.
>> agree?
>> Yeah, I can't figure that out.
>> What do you rate it?
>> This is a 10. All day is a 10.
>> I was going 8 and 1/2 only because it
doesn't have the AI thing. But like this
is This This is a buy. For 35 bucks,
it's I can't wait to take it home and
scare the out of my 1-year-old with
it. She's going to She's going to lose
her mind. What do we got next?
All right, our next product we have this
Bitbox, which I'm extremely excited for.
I know Joe's extremely excited for. I
believe it's just like a Game Boy
emulator. Maybe it does more games. It
does two joysticks. Did you ever have a
Game Boy Color?
>> Yeah, I did.
>> I had a yellow one. Oh, those things are
brick.
That's sick that it's the translucent
purple plastic. It's an SD card in here.
>> Probably need to buy it separately, I'd
imagine. They probably got us. There's
probably nothing on there. Oh, there is
one.
>> Yeah, it's in there. This is a product
I'm actually excited that it's from Temu
cuz I feel like they just fully ripped
games and illegally put them on here.
Oh, Capcom.
Street Fighter.
Yeah, this seems really cool. I mean,
there's probably other games you can
load on here. Um
but the screen, it's pretty nice
quality. I like it. I mean, we just we
we pissed around with it a little bit
off camera, too. It's
>> It's an eight.
>> I Yeah, that's fair. 100% that's fair.
What was the price on it?
>> We paid $29 for it.
>> All day. All day, eight. Are you kidding
me? I hope these things make a
resurgence. I wish like normal physical
like handheld gaming devices made a
resurgence. I don't know if they ever
will. Yeah. Eight out of 10. Very nice.
On to the next.
>> Next we've got a 10-ft one-piece surge
protector power strip [music] with 24 16
AC outlet, four USB A ports, two USB C
ports, a 5-ft
and 10-ft extension cord somehow, flat
plug wall mount, overload protection,
power outlet surge protector ideal for
home and office desktop charging.
>> [music]
>> $22.47.
This claims it has 31 plugs. Sam is not
a believer.
>> And looking at it, neither am I.
Oh my gosh.
Are you
>> [laughter]
>> Okay, so we got 1 2 3 4 5 6 12. It's got
24 if you count the six on the How is
that possible? And I just don't know
when I'd ever want to plug something
with no grounding.
>> Well, thank goodness, John. Today is
that day. Let's go, boys.
>> Oh, we've got stuff to plug?
>> Oh, yeah. You got 31 things.
>> I got 31 things to plug into it. Oh, my
gosh.
You boys are
too good to me. All right, I'm going to
stack her up.
We've got one plug.
Already can't fit that. Okay.
Or can we? Two plugs.
Three plugs. We've got four.
If I've ever seen a fire hazard
physically in person, this is it. I
mean, I'm not even needing the top right
now. This thing's so versatile. We've
got [music] the entire top of open for
business.
>> plug the hot glue guns in yet?
>> Both hot glue guns are in.
About to be dripping.
>> Did you plug that light in?
>> And that's and glue. Now, here's where
we're running into issues.
>> The blockage.
>> You know, you know, I guess just
This is This is insane. Are we ready?
Some Christmas lights.
>> Hold on. Did you plug that one
>> you got juice.
>> 12:00.
>> It's a clock Why would anyone need a
clock on there?
Woah.
Let's go. This thing takes a ton of
power.
>> [snorts]
>> What a fire hazard. I am
>> Wow, it's outputting 357
watts right now.
>> I can't believe it.
It's working. Now, we didn't get to all
32. [music]
I mean, I hate everything about this,
but you can't knock a high-quality
product. Sam,
>> Yeah.
>> give me the verdict.
>> I mean, safety standards alone, I'm
going to give it a a two. It's not even
that cheap. It's 20 bucks. You get like
a legitimate UL listed splitter for $22.
>> Yeah, I definitely wouldn't be buying my
electronic splitter on Temu, just
saying.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> It's not lying, though. I I I don't
know. I got to give it like a 3.75
just because
>> Lego gun's higher than this?
>> Yes, the Lego gun is exactly what it
said it was. This is not protecting a
single thing you want I mean, look at
this, Joe.
Look at this.
>> Tells you the time, though.
>> I also just think it you This is how you
catch your house on fire.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> This and heated blankets.
>> Some of the nicer ones, they're
literally insured, too.
>> Oh, yeah, you get a Belkin?
>> Yeah.
>> Like we have Belkins hooked up to our
computers. We can sue them
if they blow up our computer.
Who are you going to sue?
>> No, no.
>> Huh?
>> I don't really follow.
>> Huh? Next. Up next, we've got a treat
for the queen
of our shop, the Rope Halloween prank
chain.
This is a giant
fake chain
that looks heavy,
but is not. This is This is
What the What the hell are we doing
right now?
You can't walk any dog with this. You
got to walk like a literal grasshopper.
If she tugs on this at all, it's going
to snap.
>> It'll give her the curb appeal of a
Rottweiler that's aggressive, though.
>> Everyone thinks that Queasy's too
cuddly, so we must toughen her up.
Uncle Jeff, toughen that Queasy up.
>> It's a double shot
There we go.
Here we go. Here we go.
Who's the big girl?
>> Oh, you big chunk of love.
>> Yeah. Rawr.
>> Rawr.
>> You want to meet your friend? Uncle Joe
got you a friend. Her neck so fat. She's
gotten fatter, Jeff.
>> Yeah.
>> You and her.
You're too big.
>> What is it? Let's go say hi.
Is that Chris?
Oh.
Yeah.
Get it. Yeah.
>> Have it do a dance or something. Come
on, urinate. Look, it's peeing, cheese.
>> Yeah.
>> Attack.
>> [snorts]
>> Yeah.
Yeah.
>> All right. All right. Things are getting
out of control here. We We got to get on
to the next next item. Next, we have a
uh
tiny phone, I think.
Now, unfortunately, since purchasing
this,
Temu has discontinued it. So, this is
supposed to be an itty-bitty wittle
iPhone for itty-bitty wittle people. So,
Sam, can you review this for me?
>> Absolutely. Did they really discontinue
this?
>> According to Joe.
>> It's not sold anymore. Actually, look.
Looks identical. It's got the same
>> How's that possible? So, we've got It's
a 5-V
>> [laughter]
>> Never heard of that.
>> It is mandatory to use our charging
cable.
>> Yeah, it says if you use a 12, a 9, or
20-V
charging cable, it'll just explode the
phone.
>> [music]
>> Does it got MagSafe? At least it says
welcome in English.
>> And it doesn't have mag. And we got this
from Temu. You think it has mag?
>> What does this cost since it's no longer
available?
>> $29.29.
>> Put it in my hand.
>> Look at that. Wow.
It it looks like the old It looks like
an iPhone.
>> Yep. This is actually pretty
>> This is kind of cool. I'm not going to
lie.
>> So, it was 29 bucks?
>> Yeah.
>> Click that uh Oh, click the camera. You
need to try.
Nothing's working. Oh god, it's
breaking.
Why am I in the gallery now? Look at
this camera.
It's It's absolutely terrible.
That camera's
You
I
I'm pretty sure like a
old Polaroid wind-up camera takes a
better quality photo.
>> Probably.
>> Pretty [snorts] terrible, huh?
>> Curse that is.
>> The shutter's so bad. It's got this
delay. It actually worked. Crazy, it
came pre-loaded. Says buy shop shades.
It does have the old school vowel town.
Man, they could have done a better job
with the packaging. I'll say that. They
just like leaned in It's called an XS 18
Pro. Extra small iPhone 18 Pro.
>> I I I'm impressed with it. It's a little
guy. I mean, it's it's it's Android
system is kind of janky, but I say this
is
seven all day.
>> I I'm going to have to give it a seven.
It's a functioning mini phone.
>> Yeah.
>> SEVEN.
NEXT.
Caffeine kicked in. Sorry about that.
Two slice touch screen stainless steel
toaster smart digital with memory
function five bread type. Hold on. What
Why does your toaster need a memory?
>> Everything has a memory now, John.
>> I want a toaster with CTE. That's what I
want.
>> You should make
>> I want a toaster that forgets and I have
to argue with every time I toast. Six
shade settings 1.5 in wide slot 900 W
power. This thing cost 35 bucks on sale
from 220.
I think TikTok or wherever the hell we
bought this I think Teemu just straight
up will let you put any price on
something and then discount it. Like
there's no real numbers here.
>> Have you seen the real ones of these
from the KitchenAid or whoever makes
them?
>> No.
>> They're supposed to be super nice.
>> Are they?
>> So, I don't know what this is going to
be like.
Now, if you guys have been a fan of the
channel, I appreciate you.
And thank you for subscribing.
Recently, Joe and Sam went toe-to-toe on
a build-off on our build channel. And
Joe took
the dub. [music] He was gifted an ice
cream maker. But because he's such a
gentleman, he took my money and bought
Sam a hot dog roller. So, we currently
have hot dog rollers here in the shop.
Jeff's rolling the dogs, and we're going
to toast the bun
and test this thing. We got to start out
with some regular good old-fashioned
Nickles Italian bread. It's got no high
fructose corn syrup in it, thank
goodness. I never want that in my bread.
>> Oh, man.
>> What?
>> You critique the way I open a box. Look
how you open that bread.
>> I'm here for speed. Which setting would
you like?
>> Burnt.
>> This and no other.
>> Burn it.
>> Sam wants it burnt, we're going burnt,
baby.
Here we go.
Oh, it smells terrible.
>> You probably should have done
>> [laughter]
>> Smell it.
>> have done an initial burn-off.
>> What do you What do you mean?
>> OH, WOW.
>> OH, MAN, I don't want to eat anything
for a month after smelling that.
>> it says to do a first burn-off.
>> How do you do a test burn?
>> Just dry, nothing in there.
>> Where's the cancel button?
Where's the cancel?
>> 1 minute 37 seconds later.
>> Smells like the test burn
is complete. Back to toast. Sam wants it
dark.
He's getting it dark. Now, here's a
question for you and you at home.
Do you guys toast your bagels or do you
not toast your bagels?
>> I toast.
>> Toast your bagels.
>> And then do you immediately put toppings
on it while it's warm?
>> Yeah.
>> I mean, I I'm a huge fan of cream
cheese, but I'm weird with mine. So, I
don't like warm melting cream cheese. I
like the cold cream cheese texture. So,
like I'm a big on like a New York style
with like a schmear. That's not dark
enough.
>> I don't know. Look at that. How How much
darker you want it, man?
>> It's not dark enough. Look at that
photo. That that burnt. Look at that.
That looks more like this one.
>> Yeah, what the heck?
>> Regardless, we're going to try the hot
dog setting.
Even though there's a steamer inside of
our hot dog roller, we're going to try
this on second to darkest setting.
>> Oh, you can switch mid?
>> You only get one swap.
>> [laughter]
>> You get one swap.
>> Everybody gets one.
>> A few moments later.
>> I think this thing is exactly what it
said to be and it's at a really solid
price. Where you're going to get into
toaster problems. Now, look, I don't eat
a lot of bread. I don't toast a lot of
stuff, but there was a point in my life
where being fat and stupid is how I made
my money. And back then, toasting was a
big part of it. Number one issue when it
comes to toasters is longevity. [music]
We're not able to test the life cycle of
this sucker, but I would say for 35
bones, it's a nine.
The only reason it's not a 10 is because
it didn't actually burn the toast. So,
now joking fuel himself with a hot dog,
can we finally get to the mower?
>> Not yet.
>> DAMN IT! WHAT DO we got next then? Next,
we've got the only product I requested
personally and that is
a real-life bald eagle replica from
China with
a remote and a battery that actually
flies.
This is the remote control eagle
aircraft ready to fly 2.4 GHz
two-channel flying bird with dual
batteries and propeller. Features
six-axis gyro stabilization.
Easy operations for beginners and kids.
Good thing I'm a beginner and a kid.
Sam's been charging this THING UP. LET'S
GO! OH, BY THE WAY, $26.83.
SO, it's It's not plastic, it's foam.
So, we've got
a very appropriately sized miniature
bald eagle.
>> [music]
>> Yeah, it feels like it's ready to fly.
You've got this little guy
to steer it. How's this work?
>> Got to plug the battery in.
This is the battery.
>> Excellent. This is the exact battery I
was expecting to come with this. This is
a probably more of a fire hazard than
those fake batteries we already tested.
Get in there.
All right, we're on.
Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh.
Ready?
>> Yep.
>> [laughter]
>> It's stuck. Sam, throw it from up there.
>> Ready?
>> No.
>> [screaming]
>> Let's go. I'm not going to lie.
Hot dogs on the roller and a bald eagle
flying in the shop is pretty much the
definition of freedom.
The rain's pelting it down. It turns
actually decently.
>> Are you really turning that?
>> Yeah. Hey, get back here. Get back here.
>> Bring it home. [laughter]
>> rules.
>> Bring it home, John B.
>> It's stuck.
OH, GOD.
>> [laughter]
>> JESUS.
>> OH, YOU GOT IT STUCK.
IT'S ON THE SHIP.
>> OKAY, if it's got stuck on three
different roofs so far, worth every
penny. 10 out of 10. What's next? It's
finally time.
We're turning her on.
>> Wow.
>> She's moving. We don't have blades on
yet.
Look at that turn. Look at that turn.
It's a zero turn. It's actually kind of
sick.
Now, here's the thing. I've no idea what
the rest of these buttons mean.
We've got match and stop.
What does this mean?
>> Turn these for the throttle?
>> So, the throttle here is just for speed.
>> How do you get it to go reverse?
>> Oh. Oh.
>> Oh, god.
>> I never owned a an RC car.
>> I can tell.
>> We're poor, sorry. [music]
Okay, how do we turn it on?
>> All right.
>> We hear blades. Okay, Sam.
I feel like I can't I have to stand
behind it.
Too fast.
Oh, god. I'm not going to That's so
weird for me. I'm going to turn the
throttle down.
There we go. That's more like it. Get a
nice
>> Can you turn the blades up or is that
just one set? I definitely feel like it
almost takes more effort to pilot this
than
>> Well, that's what we're we're going to
test it. You're going to race it. I
wonder what you need to do to
give her a little more speed. It's just
hard to control when it's going fast.
You can just tell how shitty the cut is.
It's just like
>> [laughter]
>> It's like
massacring the grass. It's working
though, which is incredible.
We're at full speed now, [music] Joe.
>> Yeah, way way shittier cut.
>> I mean, if you're trying to get nice
lines, this is [music] quite difficult.
>> But it takes Ryobi batteries, which is
the best part. I think they still only
get a 30-minute mow time with this also.
>> We're at full throttle right here, Paul.
Do you think you can handle it?
>> Oh, absolutely.
>> you can get down and back with a better
cut?
>> Without a doubt.
>> Okay.
>> All right. This is low-key a gem.
>> It kind of is. It's kind of way cooler
than I was expecting. Are you ready?
Engines on.
>> Ready.
>> 3 2 1 EAT.
NO! [screaming]
NO! GO!
OH, you little
>> Oh, he's got to beat him.
>> I will say
>> That's kind of fun.
>> It's kind of fun.
It's impossible to get a clean cut. Like
I mean, a clean line. It's super fun
though. There's one test left.
>> What's that? The hillside test?
>> Yes.
She's going to go down, but will she get
back up?
Oh, no.
>> Come on.
NO!
>> OH, THE SAFETY TURN OFF.
It's got a safety. It was doing
incredibly
better than I was expecting.
>> We found its weakness, inclines.
Send it.
>> All right, guys. Got to get a proper cut
here, polar.
It's not built for hills, though.
Is this how we solve the hill problem,
Sam? Try to go back right.
>> Wow. Did we just
I will say the only downside to it is
you still need two hands
because
I would love to see Sam sitting there
drinking,
ripping a dart,
using this to cut his lawn next to his
crazy old neighbors he tells us about.
They'll just be like, "What are you
doing, guy?"
All right, Sam. How are you ranking it?
>> I think that's an easy nine.
>> I got to agree. Easy nine. I thought
this thing was going to be a complete
another gimmick.
Nowhere close. Make sure you're
subscribed to the channel we hit a
million. We are doing the dumbest thing
I can possibly think of, and it'll cost
a lot of money.
Until then, let us know what dumb
we need to do next. Sam, the wheel.
>> Get out of here.